All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sent sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
After traveling to the sea forest and meeting with Jinbe, Luffy and his crew learn of the tumultuous history of Fishman Island that, even today, continues to shape the kingdom.
Kizaru appears! A trap to catch Tiger!
And that's what started it all.
Fisher Tiger's attack on the Holy Land of Marie Joie and the formation of the Sun Pirates.
These momentous events, they shape the future of my people.
It's hard to believe he really went through with it.
His actions have only created more problems for Fishman Island.
It will be quite some time before we'll welcome back to the World Summit.
I don't even know where to begin to fix this.
But we share the blame. Remember, we just couldn't bring ourselves to stop him.
Tell me, why are you so adamant about this? What did you see on your trip?
I saw human nature.
Because I understood the depth of his suffering. The scream of his soul. It was unbearable.
Hmm...
Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
Wow, he's such a badass. Fighting the Celestial Dragons? Talk about balls.
Yeah, that makes it official! Fisher Tiger is a true hero!
Whoa! A Fishman's gonna wind up in the history books!
Listen, gather around!
Hey! It's Queen Otohime!
What is it now?
We have cowered, and hid, and run, and yet for what?
What have we gained from this? What good has this path done for our people?
We can't simply turn our backs on the entire world to cut off all humans.
It will doom us. Some humans are bad, yes, but not all of them.
Now, we must learn to live in harmony with humanity.
And together we can grow with them, under the bright nourishing sun.
Grow with them, huh?
Yeah, that's just too much to ask.
Hey! You two!
Sign here!
But, but I can't! I'm sorry!
Please, the whole island. Tiger's a hero to us for what he did, you know?
It's just, we know his actions might turn the humans against us. But, it's their fault. They brought it on themselves. So, we can't sign.
I know how you feel, but in seven years, or even fifteen years, you have to think about that future. There will come a day when we will be able to participate in the World Summit again.
You have to sign! For our future! I'm begging you!
I'm telling you, Fisher Tiger gets it! This is how you represent the Fishman District! He went head to head with the Celestial Dragons. And, he freaking won!
Way to stick it to those disgusting humans.
It's just like Arlong used to say, the only good human is a dead one!
Kill, kill!
Yeah, now put him in their place!
The Sun Pirates are so cool! I mean, sailing the sea, and slamming the docent down on every dumb human they meet! It's awesome!
You know what? If we were a little stronger, then I bet, we could join them!
We'll get strong! Then, we will! Take back the sea, Sun Pirates! Kill all those worthless humans!
Yeah!
Hey, boss! Boss, there's an enemy ship! Boss! Hey! Hey, guys! Did you hear me? We got a crisis!
Shut up, Hachi! Crap! Calm down! Just tell us what's going on!
Well, this is troubling. Is it the Navy?
Must be! They were flying their flag out there!
Alright, what's next?
What?
There's no mistake! Those are the Sun Pirates!
Kill Fisher Tiger!
Ha ha ha ha! Real nice aim there!
Fire!
What are you doing?! Shoot them dead!
We're trying, but they're swimming too fast!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Pardon me, gents.
You fishman bastards!
Return the slaves, damn it!
Surrender!
If you play ball, they'll drop the charges!
We're... we're Admiral!
They're... they're bursting up through the bottom of the ship!
What?
You fools!
Give us back the slaves and this will end!
Do you even realize the serious crime you've committed?
How dare you turn on humans!
Know your place, you disgusting fishman!
What was that?
Go on now.
Let's hear you say that again!
Please, somebody help me.
So slavery's perfectly legal, but freeing slaves is a crime?
And Queen Otohime thinks you deserve a chance.
Not that you'd give us one.
Now, fire!
Uh...
ányye, you're smutting the slaves.
YouTF?
Now!
Fire!
Test到 consciousness.
atomic戴 PDF
Now!
Fire!
Blow him to pieces, men.
Blew him to pieces!
We know that you're hiding the slaves!
And now, you're going to die for the havoc you've wrought!
Blow him to pieces, men. We know that you're hiding the slaves.
And now you're going to die for the havoc you've wrought.
Oh, what the hell?
These slaves you mentioned.
He's... he's a monster.
What proof do you possibly have that we're hiding them on board?
Go on and check all of us if you want to.
But from what I understand, these slaves should have a brand on them.
Do you see that mark on any of us?
Wait, stop! Put me down!
Help me!
I won't kill you. Don't worry.
I'm not a savage like you.
All right, guys. Take all their money and food and get back to the ship.
Being human is a sin.
And so, you were born deserving execution.
No, stop!
Drop dead!
Vice Admiral, Rear Admiral Cutter from the G-2 branch has been defeated.
Huh?
Why did he engage them?
I only wanted to report on their current whereabouts.
If you get close enough to see them,
well, that's apparently all it takes before their entire crew surrounds you in the water.
Oh, scary. Fishman. Guess we should have expected that.
Okay, do you have any intel you can share?
Well, the way it looks, Arlong and his men are part of the crew,
and they were responsible for the raids in the area surrounding Fishman Island.
But we have yet to fight them on land, so it's hard to tell how strong they are.
Arlong. Right, I've heard of him.
There's another dangerous one on their crew.
He's as big as Fisher Tiger and just as brutal.
Didn't catch his name.
Well, sounds like a real mess.
Ow! That hurt!
What's the big deal?
Why the hell do you care if we kill one or two of those inferior creatures?
It's not about them. You're both going too far.
Look, we're not a group of killers. We're better than that.
And don't you forget it.
But, look, brother. Sorry, I mean boss.
These humans have no such compunction.
They are actively out to kill you.
So can you blame us?
Of course we might go too far from time to time.
We're mad!
Do you want to be like the humans?
Killing someone is to kill a part of your own soul.
We are not seeking revenge for the discrimination here.
And that's not what Marie Joie was about either.
I might have broken that stupid unspoken rule,
but I only did it to free those slaves.
The Sun Pirates are driven by the idea of liberation and freedom,
not spiteful retribution.
Seeking vengeance against the humans only creates a vicious cycle.
Violence begets violence,
and I will not be responsible for more tragedy.
We'll end up condemning the next generation of fishmen to war with humanity.
Can't you see that?
We will fight and rob those who come after us,
but we won't cross the line.
We will not become killers.
Listen, brother, I think you're overlooking one simple fact.
Violence always begets violence, you say?
Well, not if they're all dead.
Who's going to fight back if we kill them?
We'll massacre the animals and force all the women and children to watch,
terrifying the idea of revenge right out of their minds.
All we have to do is show them how powerful and ruthless we can be,
and then they'll be paralyzed with terror.
They will never...
What the hell is your problem?
What is your problem?
That you, Jinbei?
Arlong's a hothead who seems to strive to make a nuisance of himself.
I don't blame him. Truth is, I've got no right to cast any judgment on the guy.
I didn't mean...
Jinbei, it's great what Queen Otohime's trying to accomplish.
Though understandably, to her, there's no difference between Arlong and me.
Honestly, there's only one thing that I'm really afraid of. My own mind.
It's taken me all these years to understand why he told me that. What he meant.
Up ahead! There's a pirate ship!
Looks like a big one.
I'm guessing they want to take us on to prove themselves.
We are really racking up the enemies.
Well, I say we seek their ship. Best to make an example of them.
We were engaged in combat on a daily basis. Criminals hunted by the world government.
Meanwhile, Queen Otohime waged her own stubborn form of battle against the world.
Sign here!
No, we won't! We don't want to live with humans!
Please sign!
Hey! The government put out a bounty on Boss Tai and Jinbei!
Seriously?
Wow, 230 million bearings!
Jinbei's got 76 million on his head!
Wanted posters! Look, they raised the reward on them again!
Even the world government is scared of them.
Yeah, yeah! They're gonna sink the entire navy!
I need you to sign it!
Let me go, your majesty!
The next three years unfolded in a similar manner.
And then one day, we came across a young girl on an island.
Mister, we could use your help or something.
Hmm?
This girl here, she escaped from Marie Joie with the rest of us
back when you liberated us from slavery three years ago.
Here, look.
She hasn't seen her parents in many years, and her home's far away.
We would like to help. I'm sure they miss her.
But it's highly doubtful we can safely cross the ocean.
I'm Koala, and I'm 11 years old.
Thanks for saving me. I'll do my best not to cause you any more trouble.
I know she's a kid, but she's still a disgusting human.
Why the hell would you let her on board with us?
Just drop it, Orlong.
I'll drop this ugly brat!
Quit smiling, dammit!
Orlong, no!
Calm down!
Let go, Hachi! I'm not done yet!
Who's right?
It is creepy how she won't stop smiling.
Huh?
You...
What are you...
Are you...
I'm sorry. I'm a hard worker.
I'll clean, and I don't need to take a break.
So please don't hit me.
I'm sorry.
I'll give it my best.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean it.
You're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
I promise that I'll never cry.
Just please don't kill me.
Hmm?
It's alright.
Are you...
scared of us?
Yes.
But I really miss my mother.
So I made myself get on board.
I won't stop cleaning.
I know if I do, you'll think I'm useless and kill me.
But I'm a hard worker.
So please let me live.
Hmm.
Well, what'd you expect?
The kid was raised a slave.
Think about what she's seen.
I'm sure plenty of her friends got killed.
And probably just for crying.
Or getting caught taking a break.
She's spent her whole life being afraid that she might be next.
Can you blame her for not trusting anyone?
Boss?
Please don't kill me.
I'll do anything.
I promise I'll be good.
I'll be good.
Pick up this brat.
I want her brought to my room.
What's he doing in there?
Lecturing her won't do any good.
The poor kid's too far gone.
Boss!
What are you doing to her?
Bandage her.
It may have hurt, but she'd never get past the pain of being a slave with that mark on her.
Hey kid, you still alive?
Oh good.
You're awake.
I guess I passed out.
I'm sorry.
But I didn't cry, did I?
So you don't need to kill me.
I promise you I'll never cry.
So please let me live.
It's okay for you to cry.
We are nothing like those evil celestial dragons.
So don't you dare act like we are.
Now watch.
I'm sorry.
But I didn't cry, did I?
So you don't need to kill me.
I promise you I'll never cry.
So please let me live.
It's okay for you to cry.
We are nothing like those evil celestial dragons.
So don't you dare act like we are.
Now watch.
No killing.
Not now.
Not ever.
Is everyone with me?
Yeah!
No matter how far the journey.
We are taking this girl back home.
Come on, friends.
You're out of me.
No Soo.
Woo!
I can't see any fails.
You're too close.
We've got some welcome.
My love.
You do best.
You're too close.
Come on, friends.
Follow me.
Help newhelp!
Um.
You're too close.
Help me.
Some finns.
After a long voyage, Tiger finally brings Koala back to her hometown.
As the young girl bids her pirate companions farewell,
Tiger has hoped that the future may bring peace between humans and fishmen.
Unfortunately, Tiger's past soon catches up with him,
and he leaves his crew with a sobering final command.
On the next One Piece, the death of the hero, a shocking truth of Tiger,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!